JONATHAN MARIN CERMEÑO

SR. SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

o DETAILS o

+ 57 3246503008 jonathan.marin.c@gmail.com

o LINKS o

https://gitlab.com/Taufiq

LinkedIn

https://fr.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jonathan Marin

o SKILLS of

- NodeJs, TypeScript, JavaScript, JAVA
- :: React, Vue JSF, PrimeFaces, Angular.
- :: NestJs, Express, Springboot, Guice.
- :: TypeORM, Hibernate, JPA, MyBatis.
- ORACLE, Postgres, MySql, MongoDB.
- :: Docker, Jenkins, CircleCl, Nginx, Tomcat, Jboss.
- :: AWS
- ::Jest, Junit, Mocha

SPORT HISTORY

(1999–2015) I was a professional Cyclist participating on international events, winning more than 25 national and international titles for my Country around the world (Australia, Germany, China, Denmark, USA, Spain, New–Zealand, Poland, South Africa and many countries in Latin America).

5 Times champion Gold medal in Par. American Championships (Uruguay 2008 – Mexico 2009 – Colombia 2012)

More than 20 medals between Gold,
Silver and Bronze at World cups, Pan—
American Games, Central American,
South American and Bolivarian games.

More info

https://fr.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jonathan_Marin

PROFILE

6+ years developing and defining architectures, microservices, for web applications using languages and technologies such as Node, React (TypeScript – JavaScript), NestJs, Express, others Languages and frameworks like JAVA, SpringBoot, TypeORM, MyBatis, Hibernate, Guice, Jest, Junit, Angular, Vue, Bootstrap, J.S.F, Prime-faces, Docker, application servers like Nginx, Tomcat, Jboss, WebLogic, relational DB like ORACLE, Postgres, Mysql and non-relational like MongoDB, AWS services. With Skills such as Analysis, Adaptability, selft driven, continuosly improving and learning new skills, tenacity and teamwork.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER, at PAYPAL, Remote

2021 — 2023

Working with microservices architecture, developing new features, version updates, fix issues, unit Testing, services deployment. Working with React, Node, and Java miroservices applications. Using technologies like Docker, Postgress, express, Nest, GraphQI.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER, at Conseres LTDA, Medellin - remote

2016 — 2021

Implementing continuous integration (Jenkins), improving over 50% deployment times.

Design and development more than 20 web applications using Node, Java, frameworks and technologies like ReactJs, Nest ,Express ,Spring, Guice, hibernate, MyBatis, Junit (Unit Testing), Maven, Tomcat, Jboss, Nest, express, OracleDB, Postgres, Docker, API REST, GraphQL, SOAP, with Oracle DB, Postgres and also some applications in . Python and with non-relational DB. Deploying on testing and production environments, cloud . services, EC2, S3, Lambdas on AWS

EDUCATION

Informatic Engineer, Politécnico Colombiano Jaime Isaza Cadavid, Medellín 2008 — 2016

MACHINE LEARNING, STANFORD UNIVERSITY Online 2018

- Linear Regression and logistic Regression.
- Neural Networks and statistical pattern recognition.
- Recommendation's System

LANGUAGES

- ENGLISH Conversational
- SPANISH Native